Hva er Bitcoin?
Bitcoin er den første
desentraliserte digitale valutaen.
Bitcoins are digital coins
you can send through the Internet.
Compared to other alternatives,
bitcoins have a number of advantages.
Bitcoins are transferred directly
from person to person via the net
without going through
a bank or clearinghouse.
This means that the fees are much lower,
you can use them in every country,
your account cannot be frozen
and there are no prerequisites
or arbitrary limits.
Let's look at how it works.
Several currency exchanges exist
where you can buy and sell bitcoins
for dollars, euros and more.
Your bitcoins are kept in your digital
wallet on your computer or mobile device.
Sending bitcoins is as
simple as sending an email
and you can purchase
anything with Bitcoin.
The Bitcoin network is secured
by individuals called miners.
Miners are rewarded newly generated
bitcoins for verifying transactions.
After transactions are verified they are
recorded in a transparent public ledger.
Bitcoin opens up a whole
new platform for innovation.
The software is completely open source
and anyone can review the code.
Bitcoin is changing finance the same way
the web changed publishing.
When everyone has access to a
global market, great ideas flourish!
Bitcoins are a great way for businesses
to minimize transaction fees.
It doesn't cost anything to start
accepting them and it's easy to setup.
There are no chargebacks and you'll get
additional business from the Bitcoin economy.
For more information about
Bitcoin visit: weusecoins.com